http://www.almostheaven-golden-retriever-rescue.org/privacy-policy.html

A
Big Thank You to Our Rescue Angels ~ We couldn't do it without you!
Privacy Policy
Almost Heaven Golden Retriever Rescue & Sanctuary,
Inc. (Almost Heaven or AHGRRS) respects your privacy and is the
sole owner of the information collected on this site. The
information we collect (e.g., volunteer application, adoption
application, donations and order forms) is used by Almost Heaven
Golden Retriever Rescue & Sanctuary, Inc. to process the application(s),
answer user inquiries and/or process orders. We do not rent, sell
or otherwise make available this information to third parties,
unless directed to by legal or regulatory authorities. We may,
however, use your e-mail address to notify you of special events
and news that we feel may interest you.
Website Content
Almost
Heaven Golden Retriever Rescue & Sanctuary, Inc. is a general
audience site.
Log Files
We
use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track
user's movement, and gather broad demographic information to
help us make our site more useful to visitors. IP addresses
are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Cookies
We
do not set any cookies.
Links
We
do not participate in any ad server programs, but do offer links
to other sites with related or helpful information. Please be
aware that Almost Heaven Golden Retriever Rescue & Sanctuary,
Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other
sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our
site and to read the privacy statements of each web site that
collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement
applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
e-Newsletter
If you wish to subscribe to our
e-Newsletter we ask you to provide your name and email address.
If you no longer wish to receive our e-Bulletin or if you wish
to have your information removed from our records please unsubscribe
from the mailing by contacting ahgrr@frontiernet.net.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy
policy, we will post those changes on our homepage so our users
are always aware of what information we collect, how we use
it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
Contact Information
P.O. Box 648 Capon Bridge, WV
26711
For the fastest response to your inquiry,
please email us at
ahgrr@frontiernet.net
Registered Charity
Almost Heaven Golden Retriever
Rescue and Sanctuary, Inc., is a registered 501(c)(3) Non-Profit
Organization based in West Virginia and is not affiliated with
any other organization having the same or similar name.
Information and Opinions; Not Offering Advice
The opinions and
views expressed in the articles, links and other material
which appear on AHGRRS's Web Site represent those of
the authors of such materials and do not necessarily represent
the opinions or views of AHGRRS or its directors, officers,
employees, agents, contributors, volunteers, affiliated organizations
or sponsors. Information that appears on this site while believed
to be accurate when placed on this site is provided on an
"as is" basis and Almost Heaven and its contributors do not
warrant the accuracy, adequacy, timeliness or completeness
of any such information. The information and materials appearing
on this site are not intended to provide advice of any kind.
Disclaimer of Liability
IN NO EVENT SHALL
ALMOST HEAVEN GOLDEN RETRIEVER RESCUE & SANCTUARY , INC.
OR ITS DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, ADVISORS, CONTRIBUTORS,
VOLUNTEERS, AFFILIATED ORGANIZATIONS OR SPONSORS BE HELD RESPONSIBLE
FOR ANY RELIANCE THAT ANY PERSON PLACES ON THIS SITE OR THE
SITE CONTENT OR BE LIABLE FOR ANY HARM, LOSS OR DAMAGE (WHETHER
ARISING IN CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) INCLUDING
WITHOUT RESTRICTION DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL,
CONSEQUENTIAL, EXEMPLARY OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES, LOSSES OR EXPENSES
ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THIS SITE, THE USE OR
ANY INABILITY TO USE THIS SITE OR THE SITE CONTENT EVEN IF
THEY ARE ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES, LOSSES
OR EXPENSES.
Links to Other Web Sites
Other web sites
that may be linked or otherwise accessed from or to this web
site are entirely independent of and do not reflect on this
web site and neither AHGRRS nor this web site shall
in any manner be responsible for the content of such other
sites or be construed as conveying any endorsement of such
web sites or any entity related to any of such web sites,
or its products or services. The links for such sites are
provided solely for convenience and to promote access to a
range of materials and resources.
Almost Heaven Gift Store
Shopping in the
Almost Heaven Gift Store through links provided allow purchasers
to donate to Almost Heaven Golden Retriever Rescue & Sanctuary,
Inc. without a cost to them! The products highlighted in the
Gift Store are offered by various companies that have all
agreed to provide AHGRRS with a percentage of the sales generated
through these links. This assists us in funding our ongoing
efforts to save more Goldens.
Guidelines
Shoppers must
access the stores from the links set up within the Gift Store
pages in order for AHGRRS to get a commission.
Disclaimer
The products displayed
in the Gift Store are offered by individual sponsors and vendors.
Almost Heaven Golden Retriever Rescue & Sanctuary, Inc.
and its members do not guarantee
the quality of said products or your satisfaction therewith.
Any inquiries should be addressed directly to the individual
vendors.
Gift Store Privacy
Please be
aware that Almost Heaven Golden Retriever Rescue & Sanctuary,
Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices of the websites of individual sponsors and vendors. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our
site, to view products or place an order, and to read the privacy statements of each web site that
collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement (above)
applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
Copyright © 2002-2020 Almost Heaven Golden Retriever Rescue &
Sanctuary, Inc. All rights reserved.
Updated: August 2020
This web set created by Kimmber Designs (no longer in business)"Specializing in canine web sites and graphic design for dog lovers!"
